const quiz = [
    {
        question: 'What food does your pet prefer?',
        options: ['Dry food', 'Meat', 'Grains', 'Fruits'],
        correct: 'Meat'
    },
    {
        question: 'How often should cats have a veterinary check-up?',
        options: ['Once a year', 'Every two years', 'Every month', 'Never'],
        correct: 'Once a year'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these products should not be given to dogs?',
        options: ['Meat', 'Chocolate', 'Fish', 'Vegetables'],
        correct: 'Chocolate'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these signs may indicate illness in a pet?',
        options: ['Normal behavior', 'Change in appetite', 'Playful activity', 'Good sleep'],
        correct: 'Change in appetite'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is best for cat fur care?',
        options: ['Water', 'Human shampoo', 'Special cat shampoo', 'Soap'],
        correct: 'Special cat shampoo'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these items is dangerous for puppies?',
        options: ['Toys', 'Wires', 'Soft rugs', 'Balls'],
        correct: 'Wires'
    },
    {
        question: 'What type of activity is most suitable for dogs?',
        options: ['Reading books', 'Sitting on the couch', 'Listening to music', 'Outdoor walks'],
        correct: 'Outdoor walks'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these types of food is not recommended for cats?',
        options: ['Fish', 'Meat', 'Milk', 'Chicken'],
        correct: 'Milk'
    },
    {
        question: 'What should you do before visiting the veterinarian?',
        options: ['Don`t prepare', 'Write down all symptoms', 'Don`t bring your pet with you', 'Ignore the veterinarian'],
        correct: 'Write down all symptoms'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these tips will help keep your pet healthy?',
        options: ['Give them a lot of sweets', 'Walk regularly and exercise', 'Neglect grooming their fur', 'Ignore veterinary check-ups'],
        correct: 'Walk regularly and exercise'
    }
];

export default quiz;